{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038775444","data":{"timestamp":" 947038775444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038788674","data":{"timestamp":" 947038788674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038801208","data":{"timestamp":" 947038801208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038810626","data":{"timestamp":" 947038810626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038824129","data":{"timestamp":" 947038824129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038839436","data":{"timestamp":" 947038839436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038842391","data":{"timestamp":" 947038842391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038852871","data":{"timestamp":" 947038852871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038861107","data":{"timestamp":" 947038861107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038870435","data":{"timestamp":" 947038870434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038872484","data":{"timestamp":" 947038872484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038883601","data":{"timestamp":" 947038883600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038891729","data":{"timestamp":" 947038891728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038901967","data":{"timestamp":" 947038901967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038903560","data":{"timestamp":" 947038903560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038915296","data":{"timestamp":" 947038915296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038923231","data":{"timestamp":" 947038923231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038933999","data":{"timestamp":" 947038933999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038935691","data":{"timestamp":" 947038935691"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038948261","data":{"timestamp":" 947038948261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038957549","data":{"timestamp":" 947038957549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038967256","data":{"timestamp":" 947038967256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038976604","data":{"timestamp":" 947038976603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038985293","data":{"timestamp":" 947038985293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038992023","data":{"timestamp":" 947038992023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039003269","data":{"timestamp":" 947039003269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039012200","data":{"timestamp":" 947039012199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039033043","data":{"timestamp":" 947039033043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039040669","data":{"timestamp":" 947039040669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039048970","data":{"timestamp":" 947039048970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039058626","data":{"timestamp":" 947039058626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039069879","data":{"timestamp":" 947039069879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039087136","data":{"timestamp":" 947039087136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039095119","data":{"timestamp":" 947039095119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039105055","data":{"timestamp":" 947039105055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039112635","data":{"timestamp":" 947039112635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039125848","data":{"timestamp":" 947039125848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039144365","data":{"timestamp":" 947039144365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039153204","data":{"timestamp":" 947039153204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039161638","data":{"timestamp":" 947039161638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039164387","data":{"timestamp":" 947039164387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039172753","data":{"timestamp":" 947039172753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039184367","data":{"timestamp":" 947039184367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039200602","data":{"timestamp":" 947039200601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039221135","data":{"timestamp":" 947039221135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039241059","data":{"timestamp":" 947039241059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039250068","data":{"timestamp":" 947039250068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039255899","data":{"timestamp":" 947039255899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039271035","data":{"timestamp":" 947039271034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 85ea1843-aec9-4c3f-9353-7fa1c0779bf5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039289124","data":{"timestamp":" 947039289124"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039290185","data":{"timestamp":" 947039290185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIYO"," userResponse":" SIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039295203","data":{"timestamp":" 947039295203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" START_SITA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039296656","data":{"timestamp":" 947039296655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039297742","data":{"timestamp":" 947039297741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039300965","data":{"timestamp":" 947039300964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039302018","data":{"timestamp":" 947039302017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039305756","data":{"timestamp":" 947039305756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039306808","data":{"timestamp":" 947039306808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIRI"," userResponse":" SIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039311226","data":{"timestamp":" 947039311226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039312247","data":{"timestamp":" 947039312247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039316200","data":{"timestamp":" 947039316200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039317249","data":{"timestamp":" 947039317248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039323234","data":{"timestamp":" 947039323234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039324293","data":{"timestamp":" 947039324293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFA"," userResponse":" SIFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039327286","data":{"timestamp":" 947039327286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039328321","data":{"timestamp":" 947039328321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039331740","data":{"timestamp":" 947039331739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039332802","data":{"timestamp":" 947039332801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039337690","data":{"timestamp":" 947039337689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039338768","data":{"timestamp":" 947039338767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039342327","data":{"timestamp":" 947039342326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039342468","data":{"timestamp":" 947039342468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 34a3d739-5d8b-4180-b2a6-9387d15761c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.si.rand.40"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039377840","data":{"timestamp":" 947039377840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039385448","data":{"timestamp":" 947039385448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039393953","data":{"timestamp":" 947039393953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039397692","data":{"timestamp":" 947039397692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039405091","data":{"timestamp":" 947039405091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039415412","data":{"timestamp":" 947039415412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039429651","data":{"timestamp":" 947039429651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039437119","data":{"timestamp":" 947039437119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039443097","data":{"timestamp":" 947039443097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039453548","data":{"timestamp":" 947039453548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039467227","data":{"timestamp":" 947039467227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039478266","data":{"timestamp":" 947039478266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039481900","data":{"timestamp":" 947039481899"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039494628","data":{"timestamp":" 947039494628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039505903","data":{"timestamp":" 947039505903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039516351","data":{"timestamp":" 947039516350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039533003","data":{"timestamp":" 947039533003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039545967","data":{"timestamp":" 947039545967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039550646","data":{"timestamp":" 947039550645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.si.rand.40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039567022","data":{"timestamp":" 947039567022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039578139","data":{"timestamp":" 947039578139"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 6bb0e1c3-5ae8-4ff0-9c8a-7175cc14f04a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.si.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_si__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039595030","data":{"timestamp":" 947039595030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 02577f3a-d875-4300-a2c3-9565cbac4b0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039630331","data":{"timestamp":" 947039630330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 02577f3a-d875-4300-a2c3-9565cbac4b0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039630456","data":{"timestamp":" 947039630455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 02577f3a-d875-4300-a2c3-9565cbac4b0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039684283","data":{"timestamp":" 947039684283"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 02577f3a-d875-4300-a2c3-9565cbac4b0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039691390","data":{"timestamp":" 947039691390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039692434","data":{"timestamp":" 947039692433"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039692820","data":{"timestamp":" 947039692820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039729703","data":{"timestamp":" 947039729703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.si.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039760011","data":{"timestamp":" 947039760011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039770669","data":{"timestamp":" 947039770669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039781499","data":{"timestamp":" 947039781498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 0a45bd0d-07c4-43c2-bed3-b0db519d61bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039806371","data":{"timestamp":" 947039806371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 9f03f4f9-20a0-4a16-9c87-15edcfa84e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" hapo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039817299","data":{"timestamp":" 947039817299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 9f03f4f9-20a0-4a16-9c87-15edcfa84e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" lori"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039826861","data":{"timestamp":" 947039826860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 9f03f4f9-20a0-4a16-9c87-15edcfa84e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039835078","data":{"timestamp":" 947039835078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 9f03f4f9-20a0-4a16-9c87-15edcfa84e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039840881","data":{"timestamp":" 947039840881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 9f03f4f9-20a0-4a16-9c87-15edcfa84e31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039858372","data":{"timestamp":" 947039858372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_lina-yale-tawi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039866800","data":{"timestamp":" 947039866800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-kile-jani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039876054","data":{"timestamp":" 947039876054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamu_tamu-wivu-yawe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamu"," userResponse":" yawe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039885700","data":{"timestamp":" 947039885700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamu_tamu-wivu-yawe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamu"," userResponse":" tamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039895741","data":{"timestamp":" 947039895741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039905590","data":{"timestamp":" 947039905590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039914155","data":{"timestamp":" 947039914155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-ubao-nanu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039930370","data":{"timestamp":" 947039930370"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039944378","data":{"timestamp":" 947039944378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039974763","data":{"timestamp":" 947039974763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039988176","data":{"timestamp":" 947039988176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" ziwe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039998080","data":{"timestamp":" 947039998080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040026173","data":{"timestamp":" 947040026172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-nchi-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040031942","data":{"timestamp":" 947040031942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 7c874e8d-15e0-4728-a70e-f0bbe4ff76cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-nchi-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040081288","data":{"timestamp":" 947040081287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6bd3f3a-0861-4991-a13f-e530f5621718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040091398","data":{"timestamp":" 947040091397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6bd3f3a-0861-4991-a13f-e530f5621718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040100199","data":{"timestamp":" 947040100199"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6bd3f3a-0861-4991-a13f-e530f5621718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040108657","data":{"timestamp":" 947040108656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6bd3f3a-0861-4991-a13f-e530f5621718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040128267","data":{"timestamp":" 947040128267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6bd3f3a-0861-4991-a13f-e530f5621718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040146851","data":{"timestamp":" 947040146851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" b78b801d-1c9c-47b0-a3e2-a6bd52126578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJA"," userResponse":" TAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040147430","data":{"timestamp":" 947040147429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" b78b801d-1c9c-47b0-a3e2-a6bd52126578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" taja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040147533","data":{"timestamp":" 947040147533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" b78b801d-1c9c-47b0-a3e2-a6bd52126578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJA"," userResponse":" TAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040176979","data":{"timestamp":" 947040176979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" c7e6849f-0978-48db-bedc-6d719ffe9109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040188075","data":{"timestamp":" 947040188075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" c7e6849f-0978-48db-bedc-6d719ffe9109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamu_tamu-wivu-yawe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamu"," userResponse":" tamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040197263","data":{"timestamp":" 947040197263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" c7e6849f-0978-48db-bedc-6d719ffe9109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040204933","data":{"timestamp":" 947040204933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" c7e6849f-0978-48db-bedc-6d719ffe9109"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040223053","data":{"timestamp":" 947040223053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040236655","data":{"timestamp":" 947040236655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040253499","data":{"timestamp":" 947040253499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040262201","data":{"timestamp":" 947040262200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040271451","data":{"timestamp":" 947040271451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ndoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040280690","data":{"timestamp":" 947040280690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040289384","data":{"timestamp":" 947040289384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taja"," userResponse":" taja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040297802","data":{"timestamp":" 947040297802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040309654","data":{"timestamp":" 947040309654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040318621","data":{"timestamp":" 947040318621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_ziwa-tuna-tawi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040337132","data":{"timestamp":" 947040337132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" taji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040346480","data":{"timestamp":" 947040346480"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" goli"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040355840","data":{"timestamp":" 947040355840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040361613","data":{"timestamp":" 947040361612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" fb4076bb-9541-48a3-8c2a-e1bf59f4b17d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040387152","data":{"timestamp":" 947040387152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040397279","data":{"timestamp":" 947040397279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040409032","data":{"timestamp":" 947040409032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040420429","data":{"timestamp":" 947040420428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" bibo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040429922","data":{"timestamp":" 947040429921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" taji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040438966","data":{"timestamp":" 947040438966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040453414","data":{"timestamp":" 947040453414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_ziwa-tuna-tawi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040462910","data":{"timestamp":" 947040462910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040473259","data":{"timestamp":" 947040473259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taja"," userResponse":" taja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040482585","data":{"timestamp":" 947040482585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ruka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040492171","data":{"timestamp":" 947040492171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040502674","data":{"timestamp":" 947040502673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" jiji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040512592","data":{"timestamp":" 947040512592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040518356","data":{"timestamp":" 947040518355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 44e0505e-aea1-42b6-b318-587e8a575d9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040544963","data":{"timestamp":" 947040544963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040554189","data":{"timestamp":" 947040554189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" taji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040565899","data":{"timestamp":" 947040565898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040576405","data":{"timestamp":" 947040576404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taja"," userResponse":" maji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040589573","data":{"timestamp":" 947040589573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taja"," userResponse":" taja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040599081","data":{"timestamp":" 947040599081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_ziwa-tuna-tawi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040607723","data":{"timestamp":" 947040607723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040621517","data":{"timestamp":" 947040621517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040631046","data":{"timestamp":" 947040631046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040640874","data":{"timestamp":" 947040640874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040650817","data":{"timestamp":" 947040650817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" jiji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040660714","data":{"timestamp":" 947040660714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040669240","data":{"timestamp":" 947040669240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040679261","data":{"timestamp":" 947040679261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" yeye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040688707","data":{"timestamp":" 947040688707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ndoo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040697804","data":{"timestamp":" 947040697804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040703591","data":{"timestamp":" 947040703591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" 4deee9bc-17e4-4090-a243-2c6fb22c29fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040733381","data":{"timestamp":" 947040733380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" eb5ebb0f-e42e-40db-b87e-1e809ade4ba9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040743070","data":{"timestamp":" 947040743070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" eb5ebb0f-e42e-40db-b87e-1e809ade4ba9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040753267","data":{"timestamp":" 947040753267"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" eb5ebb0f-e42e-40db-b87e-1e809ade4ba9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040761569","data":{"timestamp":" 947040761568"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" eb5ebb0f-e42e-40db-b87e-1e809ade4ba9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040788260","data":{"timestamp":" 947040788260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_nini-moja-taya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040797059","data":{"timestamp":" 947040797059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taji_taji-lele-bibo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taji"," userResponse":" taji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040807020","data":{"timestamp":" 947040807020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-wewe-ruka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040817576","data":{"timestamp":" 947040817576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" jiji"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040827077","data":{"timestamp":" 947040827077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-jiji-tele"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040838583","data":{"timestamp":" 947040838583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" wivu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040847926","data":{"timestamp":" 947040847926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" siri"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040857499","data":{"timestamp":" 947040857499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_siri-wivu-taka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040866866","data":{"timestamp":" 947040866866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" yeye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040876814","data":{"timestamp":" 947040876814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_ndoo-taya-yeye"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040887569","data":{"timestamp":" 947040887569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_ziwa-tuna-tawi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040897062","data":{"timestamp":" 947040897062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-ziko-goli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040905926","data":{"timestamp":" 947040905926"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_mara-ziwa-taya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040915997","data":{"timestamp":" 947040915997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taja"," userResponse":" taja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040921785","data":{"timestamp":" 947040921784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_051904"," gameId":" a6c122fe-7e92-434c-ac30-48bd8d292c95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.noShow.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_taja_maji-taja-koko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}